thisisbank.com 2018-10-12

# Privacy Policy | Search and Find your Best Toll Free Phone Number

PremiumTollFreeVanity's topmost priority is protecting your private information. This privacy policy applies to PremiumTollFreeVanity.com and administers data collection and its usage. PremiumTollFreeVanity.com is a vanity numbers licensing service provider website. By using the PremiumTollFreeVanity.com website, you agree to the data practices described in this policy statement. 

PremiumTollFreeVanity.com may collect your personal information when you visit the website. Safeguarding your private information is our prime objective and we want you to be aware of the safety measures we take with regards to your personal information. 

Our privacy policy may change, with the type of services we offer; this privacy policy is exclusively applicable to PremiumTollFreeVanity.com

### Information We Gather

We may gather some or all of the following information from you, if you are using our website:

#### Cookies

Cookies are kind of text files on user's computer that are accepted by the computer. These cookies enable us to know which pages you visit and whether you are a returning or new visitor. PremiumTollFreeVanity doesn't link any information from these cookies to your private information, you submit on our website.

We use cookies from your computer to track referrals or to understand social media usage. However, you may reject/ block cookies, where in you may still use our website, but you will be restricted from logging in to your user account. Moreover, this may limit your access to some parts of our website.

#### Transparent gifs

PremiumTollFreeVanity may gather transparent gifs, which are invisible images. This helps us gather information such as, where you are coming from and, which specific web pages you are accessing. By gathering transparent gifs, we can manage the content on our website in a better way and also, use them for our promotional purposes.

#### Registration

If any of our tax services interests you then you may choose to register, specifying your contact details. In such cases, we receive your name, telephone numbers, and e-mail address. Moreover, we receive your e-mail address, if you have expressed your interest in receiving our e-newsletters.

#### Social Media Widgets

PremiumTollFreeVanity provides links to various social media websites such as Facebook, Twitter, Google, LinkedIn, and Pinterest. When you visit our social media pages, they may collect your details such as IP address, transparent gifs etc. Moreover, they may also set a cookie so that features work appropriately. The privacy policy of PremiumTollFreeVanity governs your interaction with these social media widgets.

#### Log Files

PremiumTollFreeVanity may use log files in order to gather information such as type of the browser, your internet service provider and your IP address. This information is used to identify number of visitors and their timings of visit to our site.

#### IP Address

PremiumTollFreeVanity may collect your IP address for audit purpose, reports and to review any information. We may also use your IP address for complying with any applicable law, when you utilize our services of licensing vanity numbers

#### Use of Information

PremiumTollFreeVanity may use the information collected from you on the website, to process transactions, deliver the services or augment our services, to inform you about our services, or for any promotional or marketing purposes

### Disclosure of Information

#### Children under Thirteen

PremiumTollFreeVanity doesn't collect personal information from children under thirteen, intentionally and/ or deliberately. You must take the consent of your parents or guardian for using this website, if you are under thirteen.

#### Safeguarding your Personal Information

PremiumTollFreeVanity safeguards your private information from any illegal use, unauthorized access or any other disclosures. However at times, as you understand, though accidentally, some kind of disclosures can happen through events such as, but not limited to, casualty, hacking, disaster, theft and/ or by force majeure.

#### Unsubscribe from our Communications

PremiumTollFreeVanity gives you an opportunity to preselect your personal preferences and at any time you may unsubscribe from all communications of PremiumTollFreeVanity by contacting us through the following:   
Email: Support@premiumtollfreevanity.com   
Phone: +1-844-747-6862

#### Changes to this Statement

PremiumTollFreeVanity reserves the right to update its Privacy Policy periodically, and we encourage you to review Privacy Policy occasionally. In case, you have any objections, please send us your comments in writing else, we will assume you agree to our updated Privacy Policy.

#### Acceptance of These Terms

Any information that you provide us through PremiumTollFreeVanity .com shall be governed by this Privacy Policy. However, if you feel our terms in this policy are unacceptable to you, then you shouldn't use our website. Your continual use of our website will indicate your acceptance to our privacy policy.

#### Contact Us

If you have any concerns or questions or comments about this Privacy policy, you can call us on +1-844-747-6862 or contact us by email at Support@premiumtollfreevanity.com
